Daniel Hurtado Cárdenas

Graduated in Computer Engineer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date August 21, 1978

Address C/Pielago 3, 1° C - Ciudad Real, Spain

 $\begin{array}{ll} Phone & (+34) \; 600\text{-}382\text{-}692 \\ E\text{-}mail & \texttt{dani@cianuro.net} \end{array}$

Web page http://danicianuro.github.io

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Dynamic and used to working under pressure and in a team. Experience in customer service and great sense of responsibility. High dedication to service, able to generate added value to the organization by creating ideas and initiative to solve problems. I am an entrepeneur who likes challenges, self-taught by nature. I pay special attention to small details. I make friends easily and I never close doors to a difficulty. What I would highlight about the passion is the with which I do things.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TELCO 3.0 AXPE Consulting

2016

- Senior Software Developer
- Java, Javascript, AngularJs, Maven, Jenkins, Eclipse, Nexus.
- Weblogic, Apache, SQL, JPA, Criteria, Git.

ARCO research group UCLM

2014-2015

- Beta tester.
- Making PCB's, user control, work order degree.
- Using MVC patterns, observer design such as, singleton and agile.
- Design and implementation of communication and tracking servers.

UCLM Computer centre and service

2011-2013

- Technical assistant.
- Windows management systems.
- Making user manuals.
- Helping users, supercomputing services.

La Invencible Performing arts studio

2005-2010

- Founding partner, CEO.
- $\bullet~$ Over 500 functions performed.
- Festivals, events, performances, tours, productions in different continents.

Government of Mexico Chihuahua

2006

- Technical director.
- Artists like Joaquin Cortes and Jose Carreras.
- International festival of Chihuahua.

Cia.Nuro Street theater and circus

2003-2007

- Technical director.
- Responsible of the sound, lighting, equipment, marketing and web design.
- Managing a group of 100 people.

EDUCATION

Graduated on Computer Engineer University of Castilla-La Mancha		2010-2015
• Computer engineer	r.	
Parallel programm	ning, embedded systems, network, security.	
• Final graduation p	project: Drone Heal.	
Superior cycle on computing and telecommunications IES Torreón del Alcázar-Ciudad Real		2000-2002
• Making multimedi	a, network installation and antennas, programming.	
Computer Science and Programming - MIT The Python programming language, testing and debugging, 150 hours.		2016
Autonomous navigation for flying robots - TUM Design and development of system control of UAV's, 80 hours.		2015
Course Drupal - UCLM Design and development of social networks, 80 hours.		2011
Course of business management - Trading center 500 hours.		2004
Course of web page design - CCOO Design and development of web page, 300 hours.		2003
Course of nanotechnology - CCOO Office suites and computer management, 150 hours.		2003
Course of mounting networks - UGT Design and mounting networks, 200 hours.		2003
Course of english - $Torquay(UK)$ Native teachers 500 hours.		2000
SKILLS		
Languages Software O.S. Soft lan- guage	Django, Latex, OpenMp, MPI, Bootstrap, AngularJs, CSS, Selenium, Vagrant, Blender, Visual Studio, Eclipse, NetBeans, TDD, Office tools, Solidworks, Autocad, Git, Mercurial, Redmine, Microsoft Project, CorelDraw, VegasPro, SoundForge. Windows, GNU/Linux, Debian (Main), Android.	

REFERENCES